加油啊  查莉  快嘘嘘
Come on, Charlie. Go tinkle-winkle.
快给妈妈拉便便
Make the poo-poo for the mama.
不拉吗
No no?
好吧  咱商量下...
All right, I'll tell you what...
小便给五块  大便给十块
Five bucks for a number one, 10 bucks for a number two.
成不
All right?
嘿  请问  你们要干吗
Uh uh uh, excuse me, what are you doing?
玩电子游戏啊  这就是像我这么大的孩子
Playing a video game. That's how kids.
应该有的娱乐方式
From our generation entertain themselves.
查莉正在看她最喜欢的节目呢
Charlie is watching her favorite show.
这是唯一能让她坐在小马桶上的办法
It's the only way we can get her to sit on the potty.
难道查莉看“咯咯笑”
Charlie has to watch "the gurgles"
就是为了解决内急
In order to do her business?
没错  “咯咯笑”对查莉的确有帮助
Yes, "the gurgles" help Charlie.
而体育专栏也同样帮助着你们的老爸
The same way that the sports section helps your dad.
看这一群废物...
Look at this garbage...
又唱又跳色彩鲜艳的二维图形
Brightly colored singing and dancing shapes.
你哥俩能上楼呆着去吗
Would you guys just go upstairs?
如果明天前  查莉还不会自己上厕所
If she isn't potty-trained by tomorrow,
那她就进不去好的幼儿园了
she won't get into the good preschool.
-别这样  -那我们就要在楼下把游戏机拆了
-Come on! -But then we're gonna have to unhook the game system.
然后再到楼上给安装好
Down here and rehook it up there.
我们已经费劲的走下来了
We already walked all the way down here.
难道我们还应该费劲的走上去吗
Are we supposed to rewalk all the way up there?
其实  如果我们的房间里有台电视
You know, we wouldn't have this problem
这事就不会发生了
if we had a tv in our room.
好了  我再不厌其烦的跟你们说一遍
Okay, for the millionth time,
想要电视  没门
I am not buying a tv for your room.
好吧  我们撤  PJ
Fine. Let's go, P.J.
别急
Ooh, hold on.
圆圈圈和方块块正在为一颗葡萄而大打出手
The circle and the square are fighting over a grape.
我想看看结果会是如何
I want to see how this turns out.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第三集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E03  Let's Potty
嘿
Hey.
嘿嘿
Hey hey.
好啊  邓肯叔
Hey, Mr. Duncan.
好啊  艾薇  你在这过夜
Hey, Ivy. You spending the night?
是啊  俺们家屋子被烟熏了
Yeah, our house is being fumigated.
噢
Oh.
我猜你父母不知道
I guess your parents didn't know.
我除了是灭虫能手
That my company Bob's bugs be gone.
还是除烟高手
Also does fumigations.
不  他们知道
No, they knew that.
噢  是吗  也许
Oh, well, you know,
他们不知道我可以
It's too bad they didn't call.
提供跳楼价去帮你们
I could have given them a big discount.
他们也知道
They knew that too.
噢
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
没什么大不了的
No biggie.
今天是不是吃错药了
What was that about?
谁知道啊
Who knows?
也许是你那句“好啊  邓肯叔”惹到他了
It's your fault for saying, "hey, Mr. Duncan."
准备好迎接一条特大新闻了吗
So are you ready for the big news?
时刻准备着
Always.
好吧
Here goes.
-有个帅哥  -有个帅哥
-There's a guy. -There's a guy?
-There's a guy. -There's a guy?!
有个帅哥
There's a guy!
-跳段嘻唰唰  -好的
-Super happy dance. -Okay.
嘻唰唰  嘻唰唰
super super
嘻唰唰
happy dance.
Happy!
帅哥到底是谁啊
So who is he?
他是咱们政治课新转来的  叫雷蒙德
He's that new guy in our government class... Raymond.
噢  他太可爱了
Oh, he's cute.
等下  你是什么时候和他聊上的
Wait, so when did you start talking to him?
其实  俺们并没聊过
Well, we haven't actually talked yet.
俺们通过QQ来聊天
We've been iming. That led to texting.
今晚他想直接进入到视频聊天环节
Tonight he wants to step it all the way up to video chat.
俺还不知道俺是否准备好了呢
I don't know if I'm ready.
好了  一定要把你迷人的一面展现在视频聊天中
All right, let's get you all cutied up for your video chat.
打扰下  如果那些虫子卷土重来了...
Um, if the bugs come back...
我是说  当那些虫子卷土重来时
I mean, <i>when</i> the bugs come back,
一定要给我打电话
This is my card.
算你走运  我会再给你拿张优惠卷
You know what? I'm gonna get you a coupon.
等我拿给你
You wait right there.
机会来了  快溜  快  快
Now's our chance. Go go go go!
好了  大功告成了
All right, there we go.
全新改良的
Brand new. Brand new.
看  快看看
Look. Look at that.
现在...呱呱呱...
Now... quack quack quack...
等你长大了
When you're a big girl,
这里就是你便便的地方
This is where you're gonna go potty.
只要记住把马桶圈放下来
Now just make sure the toilet seat is down.
保证你不会掉进去
So you don't fall in.
很有希望  你只会犯一次这样的错误
And hopefully you'll only make that mistake once...
除非你是PJ
Well, unless you're P.J.
在这里跌倒过很多次了
And then it's many many times.
知道吗
You know,
我要告诉你一个小秘密
I'm gonna let you in on a little secret.
有时我来这里
Sometimes I come up here
并不是想上厕所
I don't even have to go.
只是想来这里放松下
Sometimes daddy just needs a little vacation.
不好了
Uh-oh.
你觉着如何
So what do you think?
俺也不知道
I don't know.
艾薇  雷蒙德一定会迷上你的
Ivy, Raymond will love you.
你看着靓极了...靓的冒烟
You look hot... like, smoking hot.
好吧  现在俺看出来了
Okay, now I see it.
好了  让我们看下在屏幕中的效果
Okay. Now let's see how you look onscreen.
呃...
Uh...
还不错  头低点儿
Pretty good. Just tilt down a little.
我都看见鼻孔了
I'm getting too much nostril.
好多了  好多了
Better. Better.
现在看看侧面
<i>Now let's see</i> <i>some shoulder.</i>
啊  太赞了
Ah, perfect.
现在看看你的电眼媚功
Now flutter your eyes.
适可而止吧
Now don't do that.
笑一个
<i>Smile.</i>
嘴再张小点儿  再大点儿
<i>Less teeth.</i> <i>More teeth.</i>
再小点儿
<i>Less teeth.</i>
刚刚好  刚刚好  现在别动了
That's it. That's it. That's it. Now don't move.
看着摄像头
Look right in the camera.
告诉他你在想什么
And tell Raymond what's on your mind.
我在想我卡住了
I think I'm stuck.
亲爱的
Honey,
我曾尝试着从不在你从洗手间出来后问问题
I try never to ask you this after you exit the bathroom,
但是几分钟前那怪声是怎么回事
But what was that horrible sound I heard a few minutes ago?
查莉往马桶里扔了点东西  然后下水道就堵了
Charlie just threw some things in the toilet, clogged up the pipes.
于是我准备在后院挖一个小洞
So I just gotta dig a little hole in the backyard,
疏通主管道  别慌  没事的
Clean out the main line. Don't worry. Everything is gonna be fine.
是不是应该叫个水管工啊
Should I call a plumber?
不应该
Absolutely not.
一切皆在我的掌控中
I have got this all under control.
查莉呢
Where's Charlie?
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
我的主要工作就是吓唬他
As long as he looks scared, I've done my job.
孩子们  能把你们屋里的电视关小点声吗
Boys, would you turn down that tv in your room?
你们屋里的
Tv in your room?
噢  大事不妙了
Oh, mama don't think so.
这是啥
What is this?
一台免费电视
A free tv.
-哈哈  -是不是酷毙了
-Ha ha! -Isn't it awesome?
就放在某人家的草坪上
It was just sitting on someone's lawn.
没错  上面还写着“请  笑纳”
Yeah, there was a sign that said "please take,"
于是我们就笑纳了
So we took.
你们不觉着对于这房间来说  有点大吗
It's a little big for the room, don't you think?
是啊  一开始我们也有这顾虑  但随后
Yeah, it was at first, but then
盖比灵机一动
Gabe came up with the brilliant idea.
把桌子摞起来
Of bunk desks.
摞起来  好吧  好吧
Bunk desks. Right right.
那你们的衣柜呢
Where's your dresser?
-PJ床底下  -没错  但一开始我也担心
-Under P.J.'s bed. -Yeah, at first I was concerned.
每天去床底下拿内裤是不是有点费劲
That getting a fresh pair of underpants every day was gonna be a little tricky.
但是我又灵机一动
But then I came up with a solution...
看看我们的内裤枕头
The underpants pillow.
-天才吧  -太天才了
-Bam! -Buh-bam!
每次我来这里  我都追悔莫及
Every time I come in here I regret it.
噢  噢  噢  噢
Oh! Oh oh oh!
啊  啊
Argh! Argh!
坏事了
Uh-oh.
怎么回事
What happened?
停电了  而且管道也堵了
The power went out and the plumbing.
好吧  怎么弄的
Well, how did that happen?
让我们问问那个拿着铁锹的湿身男
Let's ask the soaking wet man with the pickaxe.
还好吧  大家
Hey, everybody.
老爸  什么时候来电
Dad, when is the power coming back on?
是啊  还有十五分钟就要视频聊天了
Yeah, I'm 15 minutes away from a video chat.
还有  如果想让查莉自己解决内急
And if we're gonna potty-train Charlie,
她就要看“咯咯笑”
she has to watch "the gurgles."
首先谢谢你们的关心  我很好
Uh, first of all, I'm fine.
什么  不成  继续停电
What? No, didn't get electrocuted.
谢谢你们的关心
Thanks for the concern.
管道问题怎么办
What about the water?
好吧
All right,
我已经给水管工和电工打过电话了...
I've already called the plumber and the electrician...
噢  太好了  好吧
Oh, there we go. Okay.
...明天之前来不了了...
...Who can't be here until tomorrow...
-什么  鲍伯  -...两个人都来不了
-What? Bob! -...Ish.
别这样  嘿  嘿  嘿
Come on. Hey hey hey!
没有水和电  我们依然可以熬过一晚的
We can survive one night without water and power.
没事的  把心放肚子里吧
Come on, it's gonna be fine.
我听到好像有爆炸声  于是我赶紧跑过来
I heard some kind of explosion and rushed right over.
看看盖比是不是被炸飞了
To see if Gabe was anywhere near the blast.
我在这呢  达布尼太太
I'm right here, Mrs. Dabney,
而且比以前过得还好呢
Better than ever.
真的  没有内伤吗
Are you sure? No internal injuries?
我的胃好像不怎么舒服
My stomach is kind of upset.
可能患了达布尼氏腹泻
Might be a touch of dabnerrhea.
是这样的  达布尼太太
All right. Mrs. Dabney, you know,
我们这里可能会停水停电一阵子
We're gonna be without water and power for a while.
如果能借用下您的洗手间  我们将感激不尽
It sure would be helpful if we could use your bathroom.
直到我们的水电恢复后
Till ours is up and running.
我甚至都不让我老公用我的洗手间
I don't even let Mr. Dabney use my bathroom.
是的  达布尼太太  我知道这有点过分
Okay, Mrs. Dabney, I know it's an imposition,
但是我们有一个非常重要的
But the thing is we have a really important.
幼儿园面试就在明天早上
Preschool interview tomorrow morning.
如果我们能借用下您的洗手间
And it sure would be nice
来梳妆打扮一番
if we could use your bathroom.
将会是对我们的莫大帮助
To freshen up beforehand.
-梳妆打扮是吧  -是的
-Need to freshen up, huh? -Yeah.
我听说公车站有个很不错的卫生间
I hear the bus station has a real nice bathroom.
晚安了
Have a good night now.
盖布里埃尔·邓肯  达布尼氏腹泻
Gabriel Duncan! Dabnerrhea?
怎么了
Yeah.
说得好
Up top.
鲍伯
Bob.
嘿
Hey.
还记得当初你说我们用不到这个吗
Remember when you said we wouldn't need this?
现在看谁傻眼
Who looks stupid now?
我到底应该先回答哪个问题
Which question should I answer first?
查莉那边有进展了吗
Any progress on the potty-training?
没有
Nope,
如果没有“咯咯笑”  查莉都不坐在马桶上
without "the gurgles" Charlie won't even sit on that potty,
还有十二个小时  就开始面试了
And the interview is in 12 hours.
噢  她会被录取的
Oh, she'll get it.
因为她姓邓肯...
That's the thing about us Duncans...
邓肯家关键时刻不会掉链子的
We're clutch players.
我如今才发现
I see the light's on.
你的脸皮真够厚的
I'm not sure anybody's home.
孩子们都去哪了
Where are the kids?
查莉睡觉了  泰迪和艾薇在楼下
Charlie's taking a nap. Teddy and Ivy are downstairs.
男孩们在屋里看书呢
And the boys are in their room reading.
PJ和盖比在看书
P.J. And Gabe are reading?
是啊  他们想看书了
Yeah, it was their idea.
这么说来他们真的在看书...自愿的
So they're reading... voluntarily?
哼
Huh.
一探究竟去
Let's roll.
噢
Oh!
抱歉  我应该提前提醒你的
Sorry, I should have warned you about that.
这里怎么回事
What is going on in here?
重大新闻...来电了
Great news... the power is back on.
其实  只是我们这里有电
Well, it is for us.
你们哪来的电
Where are you getting your power from?
嘿  你们是从达布尼太太那里偷来的电吗
Hey, are you stealing electricity from Mrs. Dabney?
我们又惹祸上身了吗
Are we in trouble?
玉米片怎么还不好
What's taking those nachos so long?
外接设备太多了  不会发生危险吧
There really is a lot of stuff plugged in. Are you sure this is safe?
啊  有麻烦了  接触不良了
Ah, the problem. We've got a loose connection.
搞定
Everything's under control.
哈  怪了
Huh, that's weird.
达布尼太太家也停电了
Mrs. Dabney's power is out too.
快看  她来了
Oh look, here she comes.
你看  对于一个老妪来说
You know, for an older gal,
她动作还是蛮利索的
she moves pretty fast.
来点玉米片
Nachos?
雷蒙德会认为俺放他鸽子
Raymond will think I blew him off.
俺很可能永远的失去他了
I probably lost him forever.
如今俺要孤独终老了
Now I'm gonna die sad and alone.
艾薇  你不会孤独终老的
Ivy, you're not gonna die alone.
你可以和我以及我老公一起生活
You can live with me and my husband.
住在我们的桌球室
In our pool house.
别见怪  但听起来糟糕极了
No offense, but that sounds awful.
是吗  我觉着挺好
Well, not for me.
我有老公和桌球室
I have a husband and a pool house.
你可以给雷蒙德打电话
You could just call Raymond.
老妈  我们早想到了
Mom, we can't do that.
只是手机没电了  现在也充不了电啊
Our cell phones are dead and we can't charge them.
用挂机打啊  那东西不用电的
Use the wall phone. It works without electricity.
挂什么
The wall what?
挂机...
The wall phone...
你看  挂在墙上的
You know, the phone.
电话
On the wall.
什么时候有这东西的
When did we get that?
在我们买这个房子的时候
When we bought the house.
现在只有一个问题...
Just one problem...
雷蒙德的电话号码在我的手机里存着
Raymond's number is in my phone.
好办  只要你知道他的姓
Well, if you know his last name,
-就可以在电话簿上查到  -电话什么
-Just look him up in the phonebook. -The phone what?
好了  现在你能明白
Okay, now you can see what it was like.
生活在远古时代是什么样子
To live life in the olden days,
就像九十年代
Also known as the '9os.
哈  雷蒙德的电话
Huh. Here's Raymond's number.
-这都可以  -是啊
-What? -Yeah.
好了
Okay.
噢  按键在那里
Oh, it's right there.
噢  原来在这里
Oh, right here?
通了
It's ringing.
-俺不敢打了  -艾薇
-I can't do this. -Ivy.
-俺还没有准备好  -别扔给我
-I'm just not ready. -Don't give it to me.
你让我怎么做...你好
What am I supposed to...? Hello.
雷蒙德  嗨  我叫泰迪
Raymond, hi. Hi, it's Teddy.
艾薇的好朋友
Ivy's best friend.
没错  我想艾薇已经和你提起过我了
Yeah, I'm sure you've heard all about me.
噢是吗
Oh really?
没提起过
Not a thing?
总之
Anyways,
关于视频聊天那件事很抱歉
Sorry we missed the video chat.
我们遇到了一些技术难题
There were some technical difficulties,
所以我不知道你今晚还能不能和艾薇聊天
So I don't know if you and Ivy are gonna be able to talk tonight,
除非...除非你来找她
Unless... unless you want to come over.
艾薇表示赞同
Ivy loves the idea.
她在埃奇伍德358号  好的  再见
Ivy's at 358 edgewood. Okay, bye.
他马上过来
He's on his way over.
小泰  你搞什么  俺告诉过你俺还没准备好
What are you doing, t? I told you I wasn't ready.
但是你们两情相悦
But you like him. He likes you.
姑娘  调整好你的状态
Now get your Booty in gear, girl,
现在是时候大放异彩了
'cause it's time to represent.
不不
Huh-uh.
小泰  别跟我显摆街头范
Don't go street on me, t.
只会让你自惭形秽的
It's just sad.
准备好拯救查莉嘘嘘行动了吗
Ready for operation potty train?
-准备好了  -上帝保佑
-It's go time. -We hope.
好了  PJ  开始行动
Okay, P.J., let's hit it.
好了  嘿  查莉  想看电视吗
Okay, hey, Charlie, you want to watch some tv?
-想  -你爱看的节目开始了
-Yeah. -I bet your favorite show is on.
你看
I bet... yeah.
快来和“咯咯笑”
<i>It's time to giggle</i>
一起咯咯笑吧
<i>With "the gurgles"!</i>
小朋友们好
<i>Hi there, kids.</i>
今天的节目超级精彩
<i>Today is gonna be</i> <i>a super-duper day.</i>
为什么
<i>Why is that?</i>
因为我们要来一段嘘嘘说唱
<i>Because we're gonna</i> <i>do the potty rap.</i>
小朋友  莫淘气
Hey there, kids, don't be naughty
让我们坐在上面笑嘻嘻
Let's have fun and use our potty
让我们轻轻松松解内急
Going to the potty can be so gnarly
特别是个小姑娘叫查莉
Especially if you're a girl named Charlie.
天啊  妈咪
Oh gosh, mommy.
看来  还是没效果
Well, that didn't work.
其实对我还挺有效果
Actually it worked for me.
一会见
See ya.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
-我是雷蒙德  -嗨  我是泰迪
-I'm Raymond. -Hi, I'm Teddy.
请进
Come on in.
艾薇  雷蒙德来了
Ivy, Raymond's here.
这儿有点黑啊
It's kind of dark in here.
是啊  我们家停电了
Yeah, we're having a power outage.
给你来点结块的牛奶
Could I offer you some chunky milk.
还是一杯融化的冰激凌
Or a glass of ice cream?
呃  算了  能用下你们的洗手间吗
Uh, I'm cool. Can I use the bathroom?
不能
No.
家里也停水了
The water's out too.
噢  世外桃源啊
Oh, nice place.
我去看看艾薇磨蹭什么呢
I'm gonna see what's keeping Ivy.
先坐下吧  艾薇
Just have a seat right there. Ivy!
目前为止还不错
Enjoying myself so far.
怎么了
What's going on?
要是俺说了什么傻话  他不喜欢俺了怎么办
What if I say something stupid? Then he won't like me.
艾薇  你一直在对我说傻话
Ivy, you say stupid stuff to me all the time.
但我也不讨厌你
And I still like you.
很严肃的  小泰
I'm serious, t.
这是俺第一个中意的男生
This is the first guy I've ever really liked.
俺可不想搞砸了
I don't want to mess it up.
别这样  你没问题的
Come on, you can do this.
有问题
I can't.
每当俺对视那双棕色的大眼睛
I just know if I look into those big brown eyes
俺都会僵住的
I'm gonna freeze.
这么说来是那双眼睛在作祟
So you don't want to see his eyes.
我来帮你搞定
I can work with that.
艾薇马上出来
Ivy will be right out.
与此同时  咱们来享受下
Meanwhile, let's enjoy.
那收音机里的美妙音乐
Some nice battery-powered music...
重温下复古风
Kicking it old school.
让我们回到上世纪
Like they did back in the diz-ay.
噢  泰迪  是吧
Oh, Teddy, right.
艾薇的确提到过你
Ivy did mention you.
好了  艾薇  出来吧
Okay, Ivy, come on out.
她来了
There she is.
雷蒙德现在在沙发旁
Now Raymond is right over there by the couch.
嘿  还好吧
Hey, how is it going?
很好
Good.
好的
Okay.
雷蒙德  你说艾薇是不是很漂亮啊
Raymond, doesn't Ivy look nice?
可我看不见她
I can't see her.
顺着我说
Take my word for it.
好吧
Okay.
艾薇  你看起来应该很...
Ivy, you look good...
漂亮
Probably.
谢谢
Thanks.
这才对嘛  很好
There you go. This is good.
好了  加油  大家  继续保持
Okay, come on, guys. You've got to keep it up.
大家表现的都不错
We were on a nice roll there.
是吧
All right?
怎么还是我一个人自言自语
Still just me talking.
自言自语...
Still just...
你们俩搞什么呢
Guys, what's going on over there?
噢  好吧
<i>Oh, okay.</i>
用不着我弄出亮光了
<i>Don't need</i> <i>any light for that.</i>
那我就...我就去厨房
I'll just... I'll be in the kitchen.
啊  撞到我的小腿了
Oh! Argh, that's my shin.
我很好  我好得很  别担心
I'm okay. I'm totally okay. Don't worry.
嗷
Ow!
又撞到脑门了
Forehead too.
好了  宝贝  快去那边
Okay, sweetheart. Why don't you go over there.
-玩会玩具好吗  -好吧
-And play with some toys, okay? -Okay.
什么味
What is that smell?
我身上的味
That would be me,
因为某人告诉我没有时间去
Because somebody said we didn't have enough time.
公车站刷牙洗脸了
To stop off at the bus station to freshen up.
噢  那你就怨我
Oh, so it's my fault?
我身上的臭味就怨你  没错
My stink is your fault, yeah.
说的很对  那今晚等我们忙完这事
That makes a lot of sense. Tonight when we're done here
我就把你扔在公车站  你就给我呆在那
I'm gonna drop you off at the bus station. You can stay there.
-刷一晚上牙  -一晚上  不错啊
-And freshen up all night long. -All night long? Sounds good to me.
-嗨  -抱歉让你们久等  我叫桑德拉
-Hi. -Sorry to keep you waiting. I'm Sondra.
嗨  我叫艾米  这是鲍勃
Hi, I'm Amy. This is Bob.
而这就是查莉
And this is Charlie.
什么...
What...?
你的脸怎么了
Something wrong with your face?
没事  只是有些怪味
No, there's some kind of odor.
噢  这都赖我老公
Oh, that's my husband.
没错  我罪该万死
Yeah, guilty as charged.
我们家水管坏了
We're having some plumbing issues at our house
所以我们就没有洗澡
and we weren't able to shower.
是啊  这就是为什么我闻起来像个流浪汉
Yeah, that explains why I smell like a hobo.
并不是说流浪汉不好
Not that there's anything wrong with hobos.
对对对  我有几个好朋友就是流浪汉
No no no, some of my best friends are hobos.
是的
Yeah.
我们还是聊一聊查莉吧
Why don't we talk about Charlie?
-太好了  -好的
-Great idea. -Okay.
查莉多大了
So how old is Charlie?
已经两岁了
Already two.
她有小憩的习惯吗
Is she still napping?
大多都在下午  是的
Most days in the afternoon, yes.
她可以自己解决内急问题吗
Is she potty-trained?
-噢  当然  -那还用说
-Oh, of course. -Absolutely.
没错  内急已经不再急了
Yeah, potty train has left the station.
没错  不再急了
Absolutely. Yes, sir. Whoo-whoo!
对不起啊
I'm sorry about that.
查莉宝贝  能把电视关了吗
Charlie sweetheart, can you turn the tv off?
没关系的  小家伙们都喜欢看“咯咯笑”
That's okay. The little ones sure love those "gurgles."
-她就喜欢看  -“咯咯笑”
-It's her favorite show. -"Gurgles."
不要啊
No-o-o!
看来内急依旧很急啊
So the potty train hasn't left the station.
完蛋喽
Whoo-whoo.
好了  查莉  看来
Well, Charlie, looks like.
在你上幼儿园之前
Before you spend any time in preschool.
你要多花点时间去嘘嘘幼儿园
You're gonna need to spend a little more time.
上几天课了
In pee school.
抱歉
Sorry.
嘘嘘幼儿园和便便幼儿园仍你选
It was either that or new school-poo school,
要我选我就选一流的  所以...
And I decided to go classy, so...
看着点  你个白痴
<i>Watch it, you idiot.</i>
说到一流  好像你那俩傻哥哥在家呢
Speaking of classy, sounds like your brothers are home.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
什么东西
<i>What is that?</i>
八十寸的超大电视
80-inch big screen.
我们在一个胡同里找到的
We found it in the alley.
我们准备把它放在以前那台电视的上面
We're gonna put it on top of the other one.
我们准备弄个双层电视
We're gonna make bunk tvs.
等到我这年龄  他们一定会搬出去的
They'll be out of the house by the time you're my age.
如果没有  那就祝你好运喽  小查莉
And if not, then good luck, Charlie.
邓肯双层家居市场
<i>Duncans' double decker</i> <i>warehouse. </i>
-房子太小了  -人口太多了
-House too small? -Family too big?
那就快来邓肯双层家居市场
Then come on down to Duncans' double Decker furniture warehouse.
这里一应俱全
For all your stacked furniture needs.
想不想家里的沙发可以同时坐下八个人
Wouldn't it be great if your couch could seat eight?
如果你的膀胱大得惊人  没有关系
Got a full bladder? It doesn't matter.
记住要到邓肯双层家居市场
Remember that's Duncans double Decker furniture warehouse.
2011年开始销售
Stacking furniture since 2011.
查莉非卖
<i>Charlie not included.</i>